How was the situation with him if it was
Cómo quedó la situación con él si quedó
very bad have you talked about
de muy mal rollo has vuelto a hablar de
him again you have bug pas it was very funny and
él habis pas fue muy gracioso y
very fun all because he tried to
muy divertido todo porque él intentó de
send me with that lawyer who sent him to
mandarme con es abogado que lo mandó a
jail that I swear that a lawyer
la cárcel que yo te juro que un abogado
who lets me go to jail I
que me deja ir a la cárcel yo lo
would fire but he is a very bad lawyer and
despediría pero es muy mal abogado y
then Ah the lawyer who defended him
entonces Ah el abogado que lo defendió
in the case that he lost When it was the
en el caso que perdió Cuando fue las
things that he said to sue me the judge did
cosas que dijo para demandarme la jueza
not admit them for processing and the only thing
no las admitió a trámite y lo único que
the judge asked was that I present My
pidió la jueza fue que presentara Mi
lawyer license It was the only thing I wanted and
carne de abogada Era lo único que quería
I presented it and that's it I proved that I
y yo lo presenté y ya está demostré que
was a lawyer which is what they
era abogada que era lo que ellos
intended to say no Ah and that was the end of
pretendían decir que no Ah y ahí quedó
it then but if you had
la cosa entonces pero es que si tuvieses
the nonsense that he used to sue me
las tonterías que puso para demandarme
you would say what a piece of [ __ ] lawyer at that
dirías vaya de abogado en aquella
time I remember that he lost his temper
época me acuerdo que perdió los nervios
on quite a few occasions he got super
en bastantes ocasiones se ponía super
nervous man he didn't have a bad time in the
nervioso hombre no lo pasaba mal al
end he is an older person than me It
final es una persona mayor que a mí Te
produces in you a certain tenderness
produce como cierta ternura
no that he touches your ass like that is
no que te toca el culo así es
wonderful I love the way he touches you it
maravilloso a mí me encanta como mete
is wonderful teacan no
mano es maravilloso teacan no